the ideas are coming faster than I can
get them down on paper are definitely on
video I don't really want to write the
next one down and till I've done it
because then something new comes and I
want right in the slot
that's right mail person I get
distracted very easily you can hear the
mail being delivered to my next-door
neighbor that will then give it to me a
collaboration app help you not get
sidetracked I think we all have
different skills and I use the reducted
but we all have different abilities and
interests and what we're here to do on
the planet I think
I'll compliment each other so if you
want to write a book we need to have the
ID you need to be good at
characterization and storytelling and
grammar and stuff like just I mean maybe
not so much selling any subject but
there's many different parts of that
that you need to know whereas maybe
you're great at coming up with a story
and someone else is great at
characterization having a way to
collaborate on art projects as well as
technological projects so with this I
mean I'm an ideas person I'm not a
details person to like I mean I've made
a lot of details on the bigger ones of
like how would this work and figuring
out the ins and outs of it but finding
someone who does have the complementary
skill set to be more detail-oriented
being more of a networker and enjoying
allowing I'm kind of enjoying being on
camera ensuring these these things the
moment I may be not the best person for
it and there's but there's there's just
so many positions to be in a company or
in an art project that you don't need to
be all things to be contributing and you
could you might like that would be fun
to me to work on a story book and be
able to come up with a world with
someone and then create stories together
even if they were never published sounds
like that would be fun for me so I would
like a collaboration app to be able to
facilitate that that is Apple number 69
feel like 16 I should have been a
different Apple